

PERSONAL INFO

Portfolio:

https://turelyk-arsen-portfolio-react.netlify.app/

Address:

L-4575, Differdange, Luxembourg

C Phone:

+352 661-870-688

☑ Email:

arsen.turelyk@gmail.com

In Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/arsenturelyk

LANGUAGES

English B1.3

German A1

Ukrainian C2

Russian C2

HOBBIES

Technologies

Science & data analysis

Traveling

CERTIFICATION

Full Stack Web Developer certificate

ARSEN TURELYK

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a Junior Full-Stack Developer with experience in web development and a desire to learn and grow. My passion for programming and working on my own learning led me to the world of web development. I have successfully completed training in frontend and back-end and am ready to use these skills to develop innovative web applications. My goal is to grow, work in a team and benefit projects that overcome technological challenges.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Interface design: Experience in creating responsive UI designs (Figma, Adobe XD).
- **CMS integration:** Knowledge of popular CMS platforms (WordPress).
- Web development: Ability to develop websites and applications using HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind), JavaScript to create interactive interfaces.
- Front-end development: Knowledge and experience with React (Next.js) and Angular (TypeScript) for developing the client side of web applications.
- Back-end development: Professional Java development using Spring Boot, Spring MVC, Hibernate and Thymeleaf.
- Databases: Database understanding and experience with SQL (MySQL).
- PHP and frameworks: Strong knowledge of PHP (OOP) and framework (Laravel, Symfony).
- Testing: Experience with E2E testing (Cypress).
- **DevOps and CI/CD:** Knowledge of Docker and GitHub Actions.
- Cloud Services: Understanding of Amazon Web Services (AWS).

EDUCATION

Python course

Digital Learning Hub (october-november 2023)

JAVA Junior Developer course

Digital Learning Hub (october-november 2023)

Junior Full Stack Web Developer course

Cap4Lab course (february-may 2023)

Intensive training in both front-end (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) and back-end (SQL, PHP, Laravel) web development.

JAVA Junior Developer certificate

Driver's license B

ICT Start course

Digital Learning Hub (december 2022)

Studied HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

English learning course

INLL and Walferdange Courses (august 2022 - nowadays)

English courses B2/B1.

Ph.D. in Chemistry

Ukraine Taras Shevchenko Kyiv University (2007-2010)

Chemistry of organic compounds

Master's Degree

Ukraine Taras Shevchenko Kyiv University (2002-2007)

Chemistry of organic compounds

EXPERIENCE

Junior Full-Stack Developer Freelancer

October 2022 - nowadays

- Improving knowledge in various areas of web development and consolidating them in real projects.
- Research and implementation of best practices in development to ensure quality and productivity of projects.

Head of research department (R&D)

2013 - 2022

Kyiv Vitamin Plant (Ukraine pharmaceutical company)

- Planning, organization and coordination of chromatographic laboratory work.
- Supervising operations with equipment, calibration and verification of laboratory devices.
- Successfully implemented new chromatography methods to enhance analysis accuracy and speed.

Chemist

2011 - 2013

Kyiv Vitamin Plant (Ukraine pharmaceutical company)

- Conducted analysis of substances and finished products using Agilent 1100 equipment.
- Developed control methods according to the European Pharmacopoeia, enhancing product quality.

Chemist

2007 - 2010

Research and production enterprise Enamine

- Synthesized over 100 new substances and analyzed them to verify chemical structures for scientific articles.
- Worked on Ph.D. research titled "Heterocyclizations based on unsaturated bromoketones" and managed complex chemical syntheses.